maxhyip.com 2008-06-09

# Privacy Statement for MaxHYIP - High Yield Investment Programs - HYIP Forex Offshore Invest Gold egold e-gold, LibertyReserve, e-Bullion

MaxHYIP, will use the information you provide for internal purposes only. informations will not be sold, traded, given, provided to or transmitted in any way to other entities, businesses, individuals, corporations, or associations. You will not receive unsolicited e-mails or mailings from MaxHYIP unless you provide us with permission to do so.

Information Automatically Logged  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. IP addresses are stored in the server log files to detect server problems and also to track any sort of illegal system intrusions. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behavior on our site.

Cookies  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly and/or speed up the time of ad delivery. We use this information for no other purpose. These cookies do not collect any personal information.

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, third-party advertisers or ad servers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The use of cookies by such third party advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Policy, but is subject to their own respective privacy policies.

Web Beacons (single-pixel image)  
MaxHYIP web pages may also contain electronic images known as "Web beacons" sometimes called single-pixel gifs-that allow MaxHYIP to count users who have visited those pages and/or ad view. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information. They are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about Web site usage.

Advertisers  
We maintain our own ad serving technology and advertisers have only limited access to these resources. We do not collect any personal information for our advertisers.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. MaxHYIP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Retention of information  
Log web server : 16 weeks   
Transaction purchase monitoring service: no limite   
Transaction purchase banner ads and text ads: no limite   
Transaction purchase votes: no limite   
Email : for the current request or session only   

Children's Privacy  
MaxHYIP is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [admin@maxhyip.com](mailto:admin@maxhyip.com)  

Last Updated: May 24 2008
